e-yearbook.com 2011-09-17

# E-Yearbook.com Privacy Policy

Digital Data Online, Inc. E-Yearbook Website Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of October 15, 2006 and may be updated from time to time.  If you have not reviewed it since that date, please do so as the prior version is no longer in effect. You will not receive any other notice of changes to this statement.

Overview Legal Disclosure

We may disclose your personally identifiable information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to applicable law, comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process served, protect and defend the rights or property of DDO or E-Yearbook, or investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or violations of our Terms of Service. 

The personal, private information that is provided to us by individual members is not provided to unrelated third parties except in rare cases described below or involving possible violations of our Terms and Conditions or as may be required by law.  We do collect some data, always with your knowledge, that is used to fulfill orders and otherwise enhance content to better meet the needs of our users. We collect your information at various points when you use the Website. This is described in more detail below. 

When You Register

During the process of registering on the Website, you may be required to provide certain personal contact information such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, phone number, birth date,  password, and an affiliation.  To facilitate payment and fulfillment in connection with subscribing as a member we will request personal credit card information. Credit card information is collected so that we can process subscription fees. We use a credit card processing company to process fees. This company does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. We reserve the right to provide aggregated user data to third parties for marketing and promotion purposes but not in a form that discloses your personally identifiable information.  We do not rent, sell or distribute personal information to advertisers.

When You Browse the Site

When you browse through the Website, whether as a registered user or not, our systems track and retain certain information about the pages you have viewed. 

    Log Files

Like most standard website servers, we use and maintain the information that we obtain from your browser on our server logs. This information can include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider ("ISP"), and other data. We may use this information to analyze trends, administer the Website, track user movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We may associate this information with your personal information to resolve technical issues and support security for our users.

    Cookies

Contrary to popular misconception, cookies do not extract private or personal information from your computer’s memory, but rather, record only information you volunteer upon registering or visiting the Website. Cookies are tiny files placed onto the hard drive of your computer when you register at our Website that enable our server to recognize or "remember" who you are each time you return. Our primary use of cookies is to improve your experience on the Website. For example, storing a cookie on your computer allows you to login without typing the registered e-mail address or registration number and password. 

The "Tell-A-Friend" Feature

If you elect to use our referral service to tell a friend about our Website, you will be asked to provide your friend's name and e-mail address. We will then automatically send the friend a one-time e-mail inviting them to visit the Website. We ask for this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail and tracking the success of our referral program.

Legal Disclosure

We may disclose your personally identifiable information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to applicable law, comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process served, protect and defend the rights or property of DDO or E-Yearbook, or investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or violations of our Terms of Service.

No Underage Users

Please note that NO PART OF THE SITE IS INTENDED FOR USE BY THOSE UNDER 18 AND DDO DOES NOT KNOWINGLY COLLECT OR MAINTAIN INFORMATION ON THE SITE FROM THOSE UNDER 18.

  Communications From Us

If you have registered as a subscriber, you will receive our standard communications (e.g., confirmation of subscription, notice of renewal and similar communications).  In addition, you may be automatically enrolled in one or more of our e-mail newsletter programs.  You have the opportunity to opt-out if you do not wish to receive such communications. 

The Security Of Your Information

  We have instituted physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to store and maintain your information in a secure environment. For example, when highly confidential information, such as a credit card number, is transmitted through our Website, it is encrypted by using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software. You may also be required to use a password to access certain pages on the Website where certain types of your information can be changed or deleted. It is therefore important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password, emails which we may send you and to your computer. You take full responsibility for maintaining the confidentiality of your password. Furthermore, while we have implemented safeguards we are not in a position to guarantee that your information will be secure under all circumstances.
